
import { Question, QuestionType } from "./types";

export const QUIZ_DATA: Question[] = [
  // --- BỘ ĐỀ 01 ---
  { id: 9, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Can I have the _ _ _ _ , please?", audioUrl: "https://res.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-3.mp3", correctAnswer: "bill", explanation: "Bill: Hóa đơn thanh toán." },
  { id: 12, type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE_CHOICE, questionText: "Listen and choose the correct answer.", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-15.mp3", options: ["The train station is on the right.", "The train station is on the left.", "The post station is on the right.", "The post office is on the left."], correctAnswer: "The train station is on the right.", explanation: "Ga tàu ở bên phải." },
  { id: 34, type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE_CHOICE, questionText: "Listen and choose the correct answer.", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-12.mp3", options: ["teenager", "character", "passenger", "lemonade"], correctAnswer: "teenager", explanation: "Teenager: Thanh thiếu niên." },
  { id: 44, type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE_CHOICE, questionText: "Listen and choose the correct answer.", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-44.mp3", options: ["I'm going on a picnic tomorrow.", "I'm going on a trip tomorrow.", "I'm going on holiday tomorrow.", "I'm going for a walk tomorrow."], correctAnswer: "I'm going on holiday tomorrow.", explanation: "Đi nghỉ mát vào ngày mai." },
  { id: 47, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Big _ _ _ _ _ can throw animals onto rocks or carry them away.", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop7/waves.mp3", correctAnswer: "waves", explanation: "Waves: Sóng biển lớn." },
  { id: 51, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "_ _ _ _ _ _", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop7/bottom.mp3", correctAnswer: "BOTTOM", explanation: "Bottom: Đáy/Dưới cùng." },
  { id: 52, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "_ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-52.mp3", correctAnswer: "PASSENGER", explanation: "Passenger: Hành khách." },
  { id: 81, type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE_CHOICE, questionText: "Listen and choose the correct answer.", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-14.mp3", options: ["The train leaves at 4.30.", "The train leaves at 4.13.", "The train leaves at 3.30.", "The train leaves at 4.15."], correctAnswer: "The train leaves at 4.30.", explanation: "Tàu rời bến lúc 4h30." },
  { id: 84, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "_ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-37.mp3", correctAnswer: "PEDESTRIAN", explanation: "Pedestrian: Người đi bộ." },
  { id: 92, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Many fish and other animals live under the _ _ _ _ _ of mangrove trees.", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop7/roots.mp3", correctAnswer: "roots", explanation: "Roots: Rễ cây." },
  { id: 108, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Do you _ _ _ _ _ that education should be free to everyone?", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-80.mp3", correctAnswer: "agree", explanation: "Agree: Đồng ý." },
  { id: 134, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Go past the _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ and the library is on the left.", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-90.mp3", correctAnswer: "supermarket", explanation: "Supermarket: Siêu thị." },
  { id: 148, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "The _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ symbols on plastic help people to sort the different types of plastic.", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop7/recycling.mp3", correctAnswer: "recycling", explanation: "Recycling: Tái chế." },
  { id: 156, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Would you like to see the dessert _ _ _ _ ?", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-62.mp3", correctAnswer: "menu", explanation: "Menu: Thực đơn." },
  { id: 170, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Factories can only make new clear glass when _ _ _ _ _ _ -nine percent of the recycled glass is clear.", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop7/ninety.mp3", correctAnswer: "ninety", explanation: "Ninety: Chín mươi." },
  { id: 171, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Is everything all right with your _ _ _ _ ?", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-74.mp3", correctAnswer: "meal", explanation: "Meal: Bữa ăn." },
  { id: 176, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "You can take these tablets to bring your tem_ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ down.", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-89.mp3", correctAnswer: "perature", explanation: "Temperature: Nhiệt độ." },
  { id: 178, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "There are some_ _ _ _ _ _ parks - special places where the ocean is always clean and safe.", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop7/marine.mp3", correctAnswer: "marine", explanation: "Marine: Thuộc về biển." },
  { id: 181, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Most of the weather on Earth happens because of the sun and air _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ .", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop7/pressure.mp3", correctAnswer: "pressure", explanation: "Pressure: Áp suất." },
  { id: 191, type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE_CHOICE, questionText: "How often should I take the tablets?", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-110.mp3", options: ["Twice a day", "Once a day", "Three times a day", "Four times a day"], correctAnswer: "Twice a day", explanation: "Twice a day: Hai lần mỗi ngày." },

  // --- BỘ ĐỀ 02 ---
  { id: 201, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "_ _ _ _ _ _ _ _", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-36.mp3", correctAnswer: "RESOURCE", explanation: "Resource: Tài nguyên." },
  { id: 222, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "_ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ HOOD", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop7/neighbourhood.mp3", correctAnswer: "NEIGHBOUR", explanation: "Neighbourhood: Khu vực lân cận." },
  { id: 259, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "_ _ _ _ _ _ _ _", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-22.mp3", correctAnswer: "FACILITY", explanation: "Facility: Cơ sở vật chất." },
  { id: 261, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Do you think you can _ _ _ _ _ _ by the end of next week?", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-48.mp3", correctAnswer: "finish", explanation: "Finish: Hoàn thành." },
  { id: 267, type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE_CHOICE, questionText: "Classes finish at ________.", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-28.mp3", options: ["10 o'clock", "11 o'clock", "9 o'clock", "12 o'clock"], correctAnswer: "12 o'clock", explanation: "Kết thúc lúc 12 giờ." },
  { id: 277, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Could I have some _ _ _ _ rice, please?", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-33.mp3", correctAnswer: "more", explanation: "More rice: Thêm cơm." },
  { id: 279, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "There are five oceans, and they cover about 70 _ _ _ _ _ _ _ of Earth.", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop7/percent.mp3", correctAnswer: "percent", explanation: "Percent: Phần trăm." },
  { id: 282, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "_ _ _ _ _", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-8.mp3", correctAnswer: "BUMPY", explanation: "Bumpy: Gập ghềnh." },
  { id: 293, type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE_CHOICE, questionText: "Listen and choose the correct answer.", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-25.mp3", options: ["community", "responsibility", "maturity", "popularity"], correctAnswer: "community", explanation: "Community: Cộng đồng." },
  { id: 299, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "_ _ _ _ _ _", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-19.mp3", correctAnswer: "TALENT", explanation: "Talent: Tài năng." },
  { id: 308, type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE_CHOICE, questionText: "Choose the CORRECT sentence in the recording", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop7/coincollecting.mp3", options: ["Doll collecting is one of the most popular hobbies in the world.", "Doll collecting is the most popular hobby in the world.", "Coin collecting is one of the most popular hobbies in the world.", "Coin collecting is the most popular hobby in the world."], correctAnswer: "Coin collecting is one of the most popular hobbies in the world.", explanation: "Sưu tầm tiền xu." },
  { id: 315, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "What _ _ _ _ _ _ _ do you recommend?", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-79.mp3", correctAnswer: "museums", explanation: "Museums: Bảo tàng." },
  { id: 322, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "There's a lot of ocean life near the seashore because the water here is full of _ _ _ _ .", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop7/food.mp3", correctAnswer: "food", explanation: "Food: Thức ăn." },
  { id: 335, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Are there any _ _ _ _ _ _ _ I can visit near here?", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-104.mp3", correctAnswer: "temples", explanation: "Temples: Đền thờ." },
  { id: 341, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Are there any good _ _ _ _ _ _ _ here?", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-67.mp3", correctAnswer: "markets", explanation: "Markets: Chợ." },
  { id: 359, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Go past the _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ and the library is on the left.", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-90.mp3", correctAnswer: "supermarket", explanation: "Supermarket: Siêu thị." },
  { id: 368, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "What can we do to _ _ _ _ global warming?", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-106.mp3", correctAnswer: "stop", explanation: "Stop global warming." },
  { id: 374, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "The fruit is fresh, and the pineapple is a bit too _ _ _ _ _ .", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-97.mp3", correctAnswer: "sweet", explanation: "Sweet: Ngọt." },
  { id: 386, type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE_CHOICE, questionText: "The destination is on the left of _________.", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-114.mp3", options: ["Northern Road", "North Passage", "Station Road", "Broadway"], correctAnswer: "North Passage", explanation: "Nằm bên trái North Passage." },
  { id: 397, type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE_CHOICE, questionText: "When should I use the cream?", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-113.mp3", options: ["In the morning", "After cleaning", "After meals", "At night before going to bed"], correctAnswer: "At night before going to bed", explanation: "Trước khi đi ngủ." },

  // --- BỘ ĐỀ 03 ---
  { id: 411, type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE_CHOICE, questionText: "Listen and choose the correct answer.", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-30.mp3", options: ["There is a bus at 9.35.", "There is a bus at 9.45.", "There is a bus at 9.15.", "There is a bus at 9.30."], correctAnswer: "There is a bus at 9.45.", explanation: "Xe buýt lúc 9h45." },
  { id: 417, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "_ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-52.mp3", correctAnswer: "PASSENGER", explanation: "Passenger: Hành khách." },
  { id: 419, type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE_CHOICE, questionText: "When does she get Language Development?", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-43.mp3", options: ["All are correct.", "On Wednesdays", "On Fridays", "On Mondays"], correctAnswer: "All are correct.", explanation: "Học vào thứ 2, 4, 6." },
  { id: 423, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Are you ready to _ _ _ _ _ ?", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-18.mp3", correctAnswer: "order", explanation: "Order: Gọi món." },
  { id: 432, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Do you think you can _ _ _ _ _ _ by the end of next week?", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-48.mp3", correctAnswer: "finish", explanation: "Finish: Kết thúc." },
  { id: 438, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "The sea _ _ _ _ 's body has a shape like a fish, so it can swim very fast.", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop7/lion.mp3", correctAnswer: "lion", explanation: "Sea lion: Sư tử biển." },
  { id: 450, type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE_CHOICE, questionText: "Listen and choose the correct answer.", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-26.mp3", options: ["puppetry", "provide", "protein", "private"], correctAnswer: "provide", explanation: "Provide: Cung cấp." },
  { id: 462, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Dancing is the art of _ _ _ _ _ _ your body to music.", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop7/moving.mp3", correctAnswer: "moving", explanation: "Moving: Di chuyển." },
  { id: 476, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "_ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-4.mp3", correctAnswer: "CELEBRATE", explanation: "Celebrate: Kỷ niệm." },
  { id: 487, type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE_CHOICE, questionText: "Listen and choose the correct answer.", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-14.mp3", options: ["The train leaves at 4.15.", "The train leaves at 4.13.", "The train leaves at 3.30.", "The train leaves at 4.30."], correctAnswer: "The train leaves at 4.30.", explanation: "Tàu chạy lúc 4h30." },
  { id: 503, type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE_CHOICE, questionText: "Choose the CORRECT sentence in the recording", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop7/coldwater.mp3", options: ["You should put your burn under hot water, instead of ice.", "You should put your hurt under cold water, instead of ice.", "You should put your burn under cold water, instead of ice.", "You should put your hurt under hot water, instead of ice."], correctAnswer: "You should put your burn under cold water, instead of ice.", explanation: "Để vết bỏng dưới nước lạnh." },
  { id: 513, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Is your _ _ _ _ _ nice?", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-87.mp3", correctAnswer: "pizza", explanation: "Pizza." },
  { id: 517, type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE_CHOICE, questionText: "Choose the CORRECT sentence in the recording", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop7/feltbetter.mp3", options: ["She didn't feel better, so she get up and went for a walk.", "She didn't feel better, so she got up and went for a walk.", "She felt better, so she got up and went for a walk.", "She felt better, so she get up and went for a walk."], correctAnswer: "She felt better, so she got up and went for a walk.", explanation: "Cảm thấy khá hơn nên đi bộ." },
  { id: 541, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Do you think that _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ should learn about politics at school?", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-105.mp3", correctAnswer: "children", explanation: "Children: Trẻ em." },
  { id: 546, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Po_ _ _ _ _ _ _ is getting worse.", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-71.mp3", correctAnswer: "llution", explanation: "Pollution: Ô nhiễm." },
  { id: 548, type: QuestionType.MULTIPLE_CHOICE, questionText: "Choose the CORRECT sentence in the recording", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop7/vitaminc.mp3", options: ["Dinking lemon juice provides people with vitamin C.", "Dinking orange juice provides people with vitamin C.", "Dinking orange juice provides people with vitamin E.", "Dinking lemon juice provides people with vitamin E."], correctAnswer: "Dinking lemon juice provides people with vitamin C.", explanation: "Nước chanh cung cấp vitamin C." },
  { id: 553, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "There's a lot of ocean life near the seashore because the water here is full of _ _ _ _ .", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop7/food.mp3", correctAnswer: "food", explanation: "Food: Thức ăn." },
  { id: 556, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "The carrots and peas are really _ _ _ _ _ .", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/IOE%202022-2023/Chinhthuc/Capquanhuyen/Lop7/Amthanh/E7-QH-61.mp3", correctAnswer: "tasty", explanation: "Tasty: Ngon." },
  { id: 585, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Sadly, 54 people died, but lots of people _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ .", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop7/survived.mp3", correctAnswer: "survived", explanation: "Survived: Sống sót." },
  { id: 596, type: QuestionType.FILL_IN_BLANK, questionText: "Today, scientists use computers to _ _ _ _ _ _ _ the weather.", audioUrl: "https://cdn.ioe.vn/edu/EOlympic/ExamData/Chinhthuc21-22/Capquan/Lop7/predict.mp3", correctAnswer: "predict", explanation: "Predict: Dự báo." }
];
